### **Profile**

An aspiring developer evangelist and community-builder, I'm a hackathon organiser looking to continue supporting tech communities after I graduate.

# Developer Evangelism

### **Coach (Part Time)**

Major League Hacking

Feb 2019 - Present

Regularly represent MLH and their partners (Google, Amazon, BlackRock etc.) at hackathons across the UK and Europe.

Responsible for assisting hackathon organisers and mentoring students at events, dealing with incidents, growing tech communities.

#### **President**

Durham University Computing Society Mar 2017 – Mar 2019 (2 years)

Responsible for overseeing the society, organising talks and workshops.

Lead Organiser for DurHack, a student-led hackathon, for three years. Negotiated corporate sponsorships (personally raised £35k in total), led organising team of 13 people, doubled event size under my leadership.

## Technical Skills

#### Fluent in

PHP + Laravel 5 | JavaScript + React | SASS | HTML | Git | Python

### **Experience with**

Flask | Alexa skills | AWS | VB.NET | SQL | Java | node.js

# ROBBIE JAKOB-WHITWORTH

DURHAM UNIVERSITY

COMPUTER SCIENCE AND MATHEMATICS

## Work Experience

### **Junior PHP Developer (Industrial Placement Year)**

Komodo Digital, Newcastle

Sep 2018 – Aug 2019 (11-month placement)

- Web development with PHP + Laravel 5, React, SASS
- CI/CD with Jenkins, Docker
- Worked independently on HMRC compliance management platform for key client

### **Web Development and Marketing (Internship)**

Van Mildert College, Durham University

- Jul 2018 Sep 2018 (8 weeks)
   Took ownership of key project and redeveloped college website in accordance with marketing and
  - communications guidelinesLiaised with various departments to collate content

### **Cyber Summer Insight Programme**

Civil Service

Jul 2017 – Sep 2017 (10 weeks)

 Received training in cybersecurity, networking, penetration testing, Windows internals, assembly, malware and reverse engineering, OWASP vulnerabilities, secure C coding, SSL and encryption.

### Education

### **BSc Natural Sciences (Computer Science and Maths)**

with Placement Year, Durham University

Oct 2016 – Jun 2020 (expected)

- Achieved a 1<sup>st</sup> in first year
- Modules include Networks and Security, Computer Vision, Mathematical Modelling, Computer Science into Schools
- Expected to graduate with a 2:1

### **Appleby Grammar School, Cumbria**

Sep 2009 - Jun 2016

- A Levels: Maths (A\*), Statistics (A\*), Further Maths (A), Physics (A)
- GCSEs: 11 Grade A\* including Maths and English

### Contact

mail@rjwhitworth.co.uk